Everstov Tit

Male, 28 years

Telegram: https://t.me/mr_hardwood - preferred means of communication

Email: <u>blnaxblachbl@gmail.com</u>

Reside in: Dubai, UAE Citizenship: Russia Ready to relocate

Frontend developer, Web developer

Specializations:

- JavaScript/TypeScript developer

Employment: full time

Work experience – 7 years

November 2023 - till now

Arhcitech

Lead Mobile Apps Development

Mobile App developing on React-Native. Responsibilities:

- Mobile App developing on React-Native
- Building mobile app architecture
- Mobile CI/CD management
- Participation in the development of mobile application UX/UI design
- Code reviewing
- GooglePlay and AppStore management
- Maintaining projects

February - November 2023

Arhcitech

Senior React Native Developer

Mobile App developing on React-Native. Responsibilities:

- Mobile App developing on React-Native
- Building mobile app architecture
- Mobile CI/CD management
- Participation in the development of mobile application UX/UI design

April 2018 -December 2022 4 years 8 month

ITKitchen

Full Stack JS developer

Company works with outsource projects. Responsibilities:

- Mobile App developing on React-Native
- Web App developing on ReactJS
- SSR web App developing on NextJS
- Server side developing on ApolloJS
- Writing technical documentation (UML diagrams, Technical specifications, etc.)
- Building software architecture

August 2017 -April 2018 9 month

Boontar

Frontend developer

Mobile App developing on React-Native

Responsibilities:

- Mobile App developing on React-Native

January 2017 -June 2017 6 month

Gross

Frontend developer

Web-site developing on Angular

Responsibilities:

Web-app Angular developer

Education

Bachelor

2017

The Ammosov North-Eastern Federal University

Yakutsk, Russia

Institute of Mathematics and Information Science Specialization: Information Science and Computer

Key skills

Languages

Yakut - Native

English - B1 - Intermediate Russian - Second native

Skills

NodeJS JavaScript CSS HTML5 MongoDB SQL ReactJS NextJS

GraphQL Apollo Linux Git TypeScript React-Native

Further information

About me

My main programming language is JavaScript. Familiar with these

frameworks and libraries:

- ReactJS
- NextJS
- React-Native
- ApolloClient
- ApolloServer
- PrismaJS

Also I know SQL and GraphQL. Mostly worked with GraphQL. In addition to that I used to create technical documentation - technical project specification, UML-diagrams.